<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- From: file:/Users/jeremy/JunGroup/HyprMX-Android-Private/HyprMX-Mobile-Android-SDK/Code/HyprMX-Example-App/res/values/strings.xml -->
    <eat-comment />

    <string-array name="list_items">
        <item>Simple Banner</item>
        <item>Simple Button</item>
        <item>Simple Splashscreen</item>
        <item>No UI Presentation</item>
        <item>Dynamic Buttons</item>
        <item>Dynamic Banners</item>
        <item>Advanced Offer List</item>
        <item>Settings</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- From: file:/Users/jeremy/JunGroup/HyprMX-Android-Private/HyprMX-Mobile-Android-SDK/Code/HyprMX-Example-App/build/exploded-aar/HyprMX-Mobile-Android-SDK.Code/HyprMX-SDK/unspecified/res/values/values.xml -->
    <eat-comment />

    <declare-styleable name="HyprMXButton">
        <attr name="buttonSize">
            <flag name="small" value="0" />
            <flag name="large" value="1" />
        </attr>
    </declare-styleable>
    <!-- From: file:/Users/jeremy/JunGroup/HyprMX-Android-Private/HyprMX-Mobile-Android-SDK/Code/HyprMX-Example-App/res/values/strings.xml -->
    <eat-comment />

    <string name="advanced_offer_list_description">The SDK allows an application to request a list of offers that can then be displayed or utilized in any way desirable. Press the button below to request a list of offers. Tap on an offer title to display the offer.</string>
    <string name="app_name">HyprMX Example</string>
    <string name="banner_description">Banner Views can be added to any layout. Once the banner is inflated, the SDK will make a request to the server to get offers. If the user has already been asked the required information they will be presented with the offer (or offer chooser in the case of multiple offers). The SDK will load the appropriate asset to fill the space alloted to it within the layout.</string>
    <string name="base_url">Base URL:</string>
    <string name="base_url_name">Base URL</string>
    <string name="button_description">Button Views can be added to any layout. Once the button is inflated, the SDK will make a request to the server to get offers. If the user has already been asked the required information they will be presented with the offer (or offer chooser in the case of multiple offers). The SDK will load the appropriate asset based on screen density. Included above are a small and a large button.</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear Settings</string>
    <string name="display_splashscreen">Display Splashscreen</string>
    <string name="dist">Distributor ID:</string>
    <string name="dynamic_banner_description">Banner Views can be dynamically added to any layout. Once the banner is inflated, the SDK will make a request to the server to get offers. If the user has already been asked the required information they will be presented with the offer (or offer chooser in the case of multiple offers). The SDK will load the appropriate asset to fill the space alloted to it within the layout. Press the button below to add dynamic banners to the layout.</string>
    <string name="dynamic_button_description">Button Views can be dynamically added to any layout. Once the button is inflated, the SDK will make a request to the server to get offers. If the user has already been asked the required information they will be presented with the offer (or offer chooser in the case of multiple offers). The SDK will load the appropriate asset based on screen density. Press the buttons below to add dynamic buttons to the layout.</string>
    <string name="persistent">Persistent ID:</string>
    <string name="prop">Property ID:</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset Persistent ID</string>
    <string name="reset_uid">Reset User ID</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="splashscreen_description">Splashscreens are full screen overlays that can be displayed over your content. Once loaded, the SDK will make a request to the server to get offers. If the user has already been asked the required information they will be presented with the offer (or the offer chooser in the case of multiple offers). The SDK will load the appropriate asset based on screen size and density. Tap the button below to show an offer splashscreen.</string>
    <string name="uid">User ID:\n(can be empty)</string>

</resources>
